Resume

TOMOYUKI KASHIRO

Front-end Engineer

Birth Date 30 / 04 / 1985

Languages Japanese(native), English(conversational)

Nationality Japan

Website https://tomoyukikashiro.me

Github https://github.com/kashiro

Email <u>ksrtmyk@gmail.com</u>

Summary

I've been working on web development in Tokyo and New York for 9 years. I'm focus on Front-end web application development (Angular, Preact) but I can also use Back-end (Ruby, Python). Main business I worked was e-commerce. I made many efforts to apply TDD and morden application strategy consulting with business.

Experience

2008 - 2010

Java Engineer

Rakuten, Inc. (Tokyo, Japan)

- · Developed e-commerce recommendation and ranking system using Java and Perl
- · Managed API application with memcached and hadoop
- · Managed projects with the business department

2010 - 2012

Front-end Engineer

Rakuten, Inc. (Tokyo, Japan)

- Worked on Front-end development using standards based on HTML5 and CSS3 working with jQuery/jQuery mobile
- · Created Javascript coding guideline and reviewed codes
- · Spearheaded adoption of new principles such as responsive design and mobile first
- · Refined and iterated page speed by using server settings, cache server and front-end tool (minified source)

2012 - 2014

Front-end Engineer

KAYAC, Inc. (Yokohama, Japan)

- · Managed projects with designer and Back-end developer
- Developed UI/UX with client and designer via prototyping (bootstrap, paper prototype)
- Developed project goal and strategy with client (UI/UX and Measurement)
- Developed web application and campaign sites using standards based on HTML5 and CSS3 and featured libraries such as Angular, Sencha Touch, and BackboneJS
- Spearheaded teaching of front-end web security to the team

2015 - 2015

Web Developer

Freelance (Tokyo, Japan)

- Developing e-commerce web application etc...
- · Front-end Developer but developed server-side too using Ruby on Rails, Angular and Mongodb.

2016 - 2017

Web Developer

Material World, Inc. (New York, U.S)

- Developing Fashion Trade-in web application
- Using Angular, Django

Skills

Language

HTML	****
CSS	****
JavaScript	****
Python	****
Ruby	****
NodeJS	***

Framework, Library

Angular	****
Webpack/Gulp	****
karma / sinon / mocha	****
Django	****
Ruby on Rails	* ***☆

Education

2004 - 2008

Sociology

TOYO UNIVERSITY

My major was Sociology (Journalism).